So guys how are you, I have come here today to do some
studding on my Activa
and here the R15 is also getting wrapped, that is wrapping
going on, so here you can see
this is a bed sticker and this one at the back
I have applied it like this, you
can see it
on both the sides, so I will go home and show you the sticker
properly, I have just come home, I will
show you the sticker properly, there was a lot of
noise from the
vehicles, so I will show you
first, guys, I have just
cut this one properly, so guys, one was supposed to be applied
here as well,
but I will go and apply this the day after tomorrow,
and I have not done much, guys, if I had done it completely, it would have looked
weird on the entire body, so
wherever it is needed, that is, where it would have looked
more attractive, so
I have applied it there, so you
can see this curve here, it has come completely from here till
here, I have done the
same on this side as well,
by the way guys, I was thinking
of applying the details but I did not get the details
So I will have to place the order online first,
then I will get the details because
I did not see any good details of Activa
even online and guys, their video is already on the channel, you
can go and watch it.
Okay, so this was today's video, I did not do much,
I did a little where it was necessary
so that the look of the vehicle can
come out good. So guys, that's all the
video for today, we will see you guys
with some more such video, bye.